How's it going?
Now it's good.
It was heavy a week ago.
Then I was pretty stressed.
The heat that has been here has not made it easier.
I am so happy that it is overcast now I can say.
It is almost thunder in the air so that it is now possible to breathe.
Now it is working and now I am almost done.
It's nice.
Almost finished you say.
Yes!
What does that mean?
Deadline and the budget I have withdrawn on this project,
so there are very many who have been on me
And it has become a stress feeling.
I knew you would miss this deadline
from the first day.
I also.
It was far too much work.
But the hat off!
You have done a fantastic job!
Even though I haven't seen it see it on the inside yet.
I'm so damn curious.
I have closed again and do not want to show anything.
I want to watch the reaction video to it.
But before we go in and look so, so some stuff has happened.
On the one hand, you have no pressure left.
No, the letters are gone.
On this page I have a few left on the other side.
It has been by far the most boring on the entire building.
There are two colors on a light blue, dark blue and the dark blue.
The sticker surface has crackled in the sun so you can pick square millimeters by hand.
With the nails do not go at all.
Doesn't it work with razor blades either?
No.
The problem is not that they are stuck.
The problem is that it is so brittle.
It crackles.
It doesn't matter what technology I use one
and half an hour per letter to get it away
And I have no patience.
Is there so much else you need to do so it's an eternal job
that never ends.
Besides now that I've removed it, the cabinet is so matte of oxide
And behind it so you have stickers that are bright
And it is not possible to remove.
I have tried polish clay, I have done everything possible.
It ends with me having bought color and I come and paint.
Look what geeky!
Fy phase what bold!
Each battery has its own information display
to show the charge status on it.
So it's 14 kilowatt hours like a Nissan Leaf in battery capacity
Sisåd is 4-5 times as much as you usually have normal.
You have 2500 watts on the roof, which is also three times
More than people usually have.
There is an excess of energy.
That was the idea from the beginning.
And I thought it was so fun to drive it up there.
The surface I saved.
The one in turn is only five inches thick and as I will fold into the spoiler
So it gets fixed in horizontal position.
So it is simplified and.
Wondering how many people in the world are like butcher Star-Link?
I can say that surprisingly many on youtube
Have I learned a lot.
They start to go in and solder about components and so on
So that people can geek down in all subjects.
On this page I have.
I have an electric bike in the garage for longer tours
It does a lot for freshness and the whole.
There you have the key.
A and B are on the key.
Yes.
Remote control.
It is not possible to sneak with that opener anyway.
No, it's a winch for a quad bike.
It is very strong and works great, but it is definitely not quiet.
The quality is not the best on it.
Then it is the disadvantage that it sits on the back of the bed,
So it's basically a drum that sits on a wall only.
It has been silent it has been quieter.
and wake half the neighborhood.
They have to take that.
The floor here on the door is art material called Eva.
Eva plastic or Eva rubber.
It is a substitute for teak
which is endangered and you have to devastate it longer.
Used on large luxury hunts and so on.
Has this type of material instead of the teak.
It's soft to go on.
It is soft and it is not slippery when it is wet.
It's easy to keep clean.
You can even take it if it has been given color on dirt.
On it you can take sandpaper and sandpaper away the dirt.
It is superbly good material.
It is certainly very expensive material?
No, it is mainly 3m double -sided tape that comes on a roll
Just buy a 70 wide I think it was three meters long roll
As you roll out it just self -adhesive.
The first part is that you sit and take one berred together with someone
and then because I am about to tinker and stuff
And need to fix so you have to have a workbench too.
So then you can do so that you continue to pull it out.
Here I will have hanging off the tools and putting a screwdriver.
So here it is like a workbench and because there I have storage.
It is four and a half meters of box that I have the opportunity
to have storage in.
One -third of the kitchen floor I use all the way to
to almost all the way to the back wall.
This is an electric bike.
Yes, it is an almost legal electric bike.
It is just over 250 watts, rather EU mop in performance,
But it is really easy to carry.
It is collapsible, but I do not need to fold it in the middle.
It is a detachable rule.
What is the range of things like this?
I have tested it without treading and it does somewhere around 50 km/h
So it is about five miles reach.
Not so much bike left of it.
Think it will cycle something?
Or will you just slide around.
The tramps are only symbolic.
I have three transport opportunities and the truck is one.
If you are in a small town small town, it can be crowded and booky.
I have the electric bike for long excursions, the scooter for short quick travel
Around different purposes with them.
But you have a regular interior door for the front door.
Inner door because I have the back tilp to fold
So it is technically speaking in, it is inside.
Welcome Tom My Crib!
Here it was cold!
It is also flexible and you can paint around round corners
And everything.
I love concrete so it's really cool to have it on all the cabinets
Then all horizontal surfaces, powder coated sheet,
Everything up to every 3D cork I am happy with it creates.
Without it, it is a very soft sound in here.
So the feeling now is a bit biased
But the feeling you come in is more apartment than a camper.
One of the reasons for everything taking such time
Is that everything is handmade.
I have not bought ready -made cabinets for there are no cabinets
Which is in line with the dimensions I wanted.
Everything from doors to cabinets.
The body and everything is handmade by me and it is an immense time.
Two pieces in the kitchen that are from IKEA.
That's the only thing that is bought.
Every gadget in here I have done to get what I want it.
Is it difficult to get it on film should you have an outdoor feeling indoors?
After all, it is Moldak's modules that are LED panels with high resolution photo
In front that creates a feeling of skylights.
In the peripheral vision you get a volume feel.
But it is still just a common lighting.
The reason I have this is of course
Because I have covered the entire roof with solar panels.
A wider bed and so I have removed ten centimeters
on the shower instead of a 90 wide.
Has an 80 wide.
It is good enough.
This in turn means I have ten centimeters
Wider kitchen counter.
So when I have lived in the box I have adjusted the drawing
So it has worked great.
Saw it on Youtube that the submarines have red light
Not to ruin the darkness so I did the same.
Now I extinguish here.
Then I have red led lights in two places
In the camper when you need to go to Pinka at night.
But the red light you find.
The fake wall I built expands 150 millimeters
and a side effect of it is that it looks like the air heat pump
is penetrated into the corner.
The invert to the solar panels get hot
and therefore I have a cooling directly from the AC
to an inverter that cools down the entire plant
So they cooperate.
In winter I have run air air heat pump with heat
So I have heat as well as any and the same thing now in the summer
Who cools just as well.
To tinker with something.
However, we have.
This is the bathroom.
Should there be burglary here, no one finds the bathroom.
No, but you have no shower in the ceiling but you run with hand shower.
Then I have a loose shower curtain that you pull for.
The shower is pretty special because it is a hybrid solution.
When I shower I pull out in the closet,
Pulls out the refrigerator so I have room and can shower.
Now it was a strange sound.
This was a strange error.
And the need for the toilet in this is behind it.
Because it is the extra job to pull it out.
I don't think you care about that.
Especially not when you are in a hurry.
Then you have to prioritize other things.
This is my toothbrush and toothpaste and to make
themselves in order in the morning.
So there you have that part.
Directly left in the sink, you should wash and all this.
So this will be my bathroom.
Bathroom, separate toilet separately.
But it is the final thing is related to the entire kitchen department
So it will be tomorrow's job the kitchen table that I talked about is burnt wood.
Powder coated steel sheet in the center and then you have the outer edge
with burnt wood.
For me, the bed and the tables are.
The two fixed points that I do not want to compromise with.
So therefore a large table and it is an extremely stable table.
It in turn means that when I work that way.
Folds the screen.
Folds it out.
How can you sit and youtuba there?
Here I will sit and cut when I have more time.
Looking forward.
How did it go for you to film during this project?
I have accumulated a lot of material and I have consciously chosen
Not to cut anything and not post anything
And then you probably produce lots of materials too.
Yeah, I've started to put out material on it
and it is while I built the box so that the next change on the channel
Become the building of the motorhome and then change.
Another change later on will be more a travel related youtube channel
so the channel is the same, but the content will shift some neighborly dependent
on the fact that there are different phases of the trip.
Can you see you get angry and so there?
So I get angry.
I have cut away everything like everything works on the first attempt,
As it always does in reality.
Where will be the first trip by the way?
Exotic.
Umeå!
I'll be north and say goodbye and say goodbye to family and friends
And then I pull Norway south, down in Europe.
But I thought like this when you leave Sweden now,
Which you do soon and is away when you come back,
Then I want to know how it went, how you have been
And worked and how you met people and stuff.
So please feel free to contact me then
So we do a follow -up to it.
Preferably because it may be interesting to see how the stuff holds together
And if it has become as I imagined.
I am extremely impressed!
Hat off!
Thanks!
And good luck!
Great to be able to follow this, really.
It has been an interesting project and I have received very
Very new friends on the journey.
Very very curious people.
Have just found a motorhome in the middle of the central town.
It has been mixed results.
I have sabotaged a lot of things.
Things have been broken, I have had to rebuild and change
And that's part of the test process.
But on the whole it was very successful.
The difficult thing about the building I have discovered is to build just.
Some things are oversized and others are under -dimensioned.
And so it can be.
But I am very pleased.
We'll see if there will be more updates, but have gone!